<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WinningRecipe</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="recipe_name">Recipe Name</string>
    <string name="instructions">Prepare the Patties:\n\nTake the ground beef and shape it into burger patties. You can typically make them about 1/3 to ½ pound (150–225 grams) each, depending on your preference.\n\nSeason both sides of each patty with salt and pepper. You can also add other seasonings or spices if you like.Heat the Grill or Pan:\n\n\nPreheat your grill or a skillet over medium–high heat. Make sure it\'s hot before you start cooking.\n\nCook the Patties:\n\n\nPlace the burger patties on the grill or in the skillet.\n\nFor medium–rare burgers, cook for about 3–4 minutes per side.\n\nFor medium burgers, cook for about 4–5 minutes per side.\n\nFor well-done burgers, cook for about 6-7 minutes per side.\n\nAdd cheese slices on top of the patties during the last minute of cooking to melt.\n\nToast the Buns:\n\nWhile the patties are cooking, split the hamburger buns in half.\n\nPlace the bun halves on the grill or in a toaster for a minute or so to lightly toast them. This adds a nice crunch to the burger.\n\nAssemble the Burger:\n\nBegin assembling your burger on the bottom half of the toasted bun.\n\nStart with a lettuce leaf, followed by a slice of tomato and onion. Add pickles if desired.\n\nPlace the cooked patty with melted cheese on top of the veggies.\n\nAdd Condiments:\n\nSquirt ketchup, mustard, and mayonnaise (if using) on the patty.\n\nTop it Off:\n\nPlace the top half of the bun on the condiments to complete the burger.\n\nServe and Enjoy:\n\nYour classic hamburger is now ready to be enjoyed! Serve it with your favorite sides like French fries, coleslaw, or a salad.\nFeel free to customize your burger with additional toppings and condiments to suit your taste. Enjoy your delicious homemade hamburger!</string>
    <string name="ingredients">  Ground beef\nSalt and pepper\nHamburger buns\nLettuce leaves\nTomato slices\nOnion slices\nPickles (optional)\nCheese slices\nKetchup\nMustard\nMayonnaise (optional)</string>
</resources>